{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Exterior Shutter Installation Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/82440/":{"taskOID":82440,"originalTaskOID":82440,"setID":777,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4726,"questionDisplayText":"Window Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the window sizes for which you need shutters.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"2' x 2'","answerDisplayText":"2' x 2'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":442,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3' x 3'","answerDisplayText":"3' x 3'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":443,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3' x 4'","answerDisplayText":"3' x 4'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"3' x 5'","answerDisplayText":"3' x 5'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":482,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"4' x 6'","answerDisplayText":"4' x 6'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":540,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"6' x 8'","answerDisplayText":"6' x 8'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4727,"questionDisplayText":"Material and Finish","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of material and finish do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4717,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plastic","answerDisplayText":"Plastic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4552,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Painted","answerDisplayText":"Painted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6010,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stained","answerDisplayText":"Stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4728,"questionDisplayText":"Match Existing Shutters","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do the shutters need to match existing shutters?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4726,"questionDisplayText":"Window Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the window sizes for which you need shutters.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"2' x 2'","answerDisplayText":"2' x 2'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":442,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3' x 3'","answerDisplayText":"3' x 3'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":443,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3' x 4'","answerDisplayText":"3' x 4'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"3' x 5'","answerDisplayText":"3' x 5'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":482,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"4' x 6'","answerDisplayText":"4' x 6'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":540,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"6' x 8'","answerDisplayText":"6' x 8'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"2' x 2'","answerDisplayText":"2' x 2'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":442,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3' x 3'","answerDisplayText":"3' x 3'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":443,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3' x 4'","answerDisplayText":"3' x 4'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"3' x 5'","answerDisplayText":"3' x 5'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":482,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"4' x 6'","answerDisplayText":"4' x 6'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":540,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"6' x 8'","answerDisplayText":"6' x 8'","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4727,"questionDisplayText":"Material and Finish","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of material and finish do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4717,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plastic","answerDisplayText":"Plastic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4552,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Painted","answerDisplayText":"Painted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6010,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stained","answerDisplayText":"Stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4717,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plastic","answerDisplayText":"Plastic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4552,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Painted","answerDisplayText":"Painted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6010,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stained","answerDisplayText":"Stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4728,"questionDisplayText":"Match Existing Shutters","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do the shutters need to match existing shutters?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/82440/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":82440,"taskName":"Exterior Shutters - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Exterior Window Shutters","xmTaskDescriptor":"Exterior Shutter Installation Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":5113,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carpenters window Shutters Exterior","textMessagingName":"Inst Ext Shutters","rolloverLongDesc":"Refers to the mostly decorative louvered vertical rectangles that flank windows \u0026 doors, especially on the front of a home. Older shutters swing on hinges allowing them to be closed for storm protection or to reduce daytime sunlight penetration. Most modern shutters are purely decorative \u0026 are screwed to the wall \u0026 do not close.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes vinyl, aluminum \u0026 wood types.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Exterior Window Shutters.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Exterior Shutter Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Exterior Shutters","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":9,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects that require help, you might consider ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"requesting a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Exterior Shutters Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Exterior Shutters - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Exterior Shutter Project","urlName":"Exterior-Shutters-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Exterior Shutter Installation Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Carpenters,window,Shutters,Exterior","emcCategoryOid":-12010,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":777,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isCookielessUser":true}